You are beating a police?
You scumbag!
What were you thinking? To hit police.
How dare you strike at police?
Hold him tight.
Scoundrel!
How could you hit police?
What was on your mind?
How old do you think you are?
Bloody dog!
There is no entry in the book, right?
Hmm...
Let's do it.
First, we have to give him good.
Hey, can't you see?
I'm eating.
You dropped my food.
Do you think you are at home?
To eat and relax.
Wasn't lastnight enough?
Hey, what are you saying?
We are in your area by accident.
Had we been at Dhoolpet station,
they'd treat us with drinks and snacks.
That's who Don Chintu is!
Do you get it?
Right.
You get it?
Is it?
We too would like to spoil your boss, Chintanna.
Should we?
Aye!
Keep quiet.
Leave it.
You please carry on.
Beaten to pulp
yet this fool is smiling.
He looks like a pothead.
What do you smoke?
Is it sweet or sour?
Tell me.
Hey, it's not sweet or sour.
I will tell you.
He is drunk in love.
It is an intoxication without cure.
Love drunk?
How can you determine the issue
so easily, Chintanna? Wow!
He is quite capable of it.
He can tell about a guy from his face
and a woman from her grace...
-He can look and tell.
-That's right.
In that case, brother,
can you read mine?
You stupid piece of shit!
Are you a woman?
You rogue!
Let him talk, not me.
Hey, brother, tell everyone
about your love story.
Go on, share it.
-There is no love story.
-Come on, tell us about it.
Brother is asking.
Spill the beans.
-Tell us, dear.
-Please brother.
Let out now.
Hey, tell us.
Chintanna is asking.
Share it with us.
Hey, there is no love story
as you are thinking.
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay, okay, okay.
I will tell.
Since childhood, I’ve been captivated by beauty.
Cigarettes and alcohol, maybe not…
but when it comes to beauty, we’re addicted.
Hey, you guys might think this is all
pretty common for a 20-year-old guy.
But for me, it’s something else entirely…
it feels like an addiction.
When it comes to beauty…
Every morning I wake up just to cook,
pack lunch, carry water...
I break myself doing everything.
But no one cares.
Look at him... not a care in the world.
Just on his phone all the time.
Goes out with his boys...
And get into unnecessary fights.
Doesn't ever both to help.
Hey!
Why don't you fetch some water?
No way, dad.
You do it!
It's all just uncles and aunties carrying water.
My legs are really hurting anyway.
I couldn't sleep all night.
Why didn't tell me?
Why are your legs hurting?
Let me massage.
Place your legs here.
No need to massage, just sit on them
for a bit.
Hmm.
Put some weight and sit.
-Ah…
-Why are you groaning like an old guy?
Oh!
I wear myself out pressing his legs,
-and you're making him press your's?
-This lady is always disturbing me.
What a guy!
Daddy, sit properly!
Can you?
Use more weight.
Wow!
And the award for the best father goes to..
Mr. Shekhar.
Wow!
-Aunty...
-Yes?
The water flow has dropped.
-Huh?
-Give it to me.
Go and take some rest.
You should tell me
when there's work, Mom.
Why exhaust yourself?
I will take care of it.
“Any little bug that crawls into my head
turns my focus completely toward the ladies”
“Even a glimpse of delicate feet adorned with toe rings
sends my heart completely out of control”
“The more I grow,
the more my fascinations revolve around beauty"
Why didn't you call me?
Oh!
Your clothes will get wet.
-Aren’t you getting late?
-It’s okay.
I’ll go now. Come.
"My roaming eyes keep finding their way to beauty"
What a lucky guy!
This short guy.
Oh! He is here.
Are you done?
Let's go.
Hey, Vikrant.
Wait a minute.
Coming.
He is Ram Singh.
Vikram's elder brother.
He is the president of the Miser’s Association.
What is it?
Take this Rs.5 and go to the shop.
And bring me a packet of incense, camphor,
turmeric powder, vermilion...
..and a little oil and a banana.
Go and get it.
Get all this in Rs.5?
Or should I give you Rs.100?
Are you praying or trying to confuse me?
Yeah right!
You tell me what I should do.
You go and get it.
Doesn't earn a penny
but he is full of pride.
-Daddy.
-Hmm..
Should I drop you?
Why bother?
You probably have a hundred things
to take care of. Carry on.
-Greetings, Shekhar brother.
-Hi there.
Going to the shop?
Where else? Can't avoid.
Are you going to the office?
No, I've an earring.
I'll go to court and then to office.
-Greetings, Lal.
-Greetings.
What's up, hero?
Damn!
God bless your sweet romance.
Did you see that guy, Lal?
All his eyes are on you
like a watch dog.
He is not just a retired police constable.
He is a retired police dog.
Wonder what he is up to.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Hey, fatso.
What's up?
Are you carrying?
Sure.
I'm in my 7th month.
Throw me a baby shower.
Why should we?
Ask the one who did it.
-Hmm! Aren’t you the one who did it?
-Get lost. Move.
-Am I wrong?
-Get on.
Hey! What is it with him?
Why is he shaving everyday?
-Mom.
-Hmm.
What is this?
Tell him please.
To stop this 'ex-mission' everyday.
Hey! It is not ex-mission.
It is exhibition.
You are good for nothing.
-Mom took off.
-All three of you have no shame.
-Get on.
-How can you say that to him?
Calling it an exhibition...
These are the friends I have had
since my birth.
Although we are three, we are one soul.
We have two bikes
but we ride together on one.
We share our tea too.
One by three.
Sitting here everyday,
we turned this cafe into a casino.
We used this matchbox for gambling.
These are the crooks in our stress free life.
They are Tony's boys.
Always up to no good.
One day, we will smash them.
Here you go.
Jackpot!
Bro...
It fell.
Wow!
Yay!
This is what you call a jackpot.
He blew on it.
Collect the money.
Take it.
He blew it down.
Hey, what are you saying?!
-Oh, damn...
-He blew on it and I saw him do it.
You try to cheat me?
You rascal!
Hands off him, you idiot!
-What is this?
-Hold him down.
Come here, you fatso.
Where are you running?
Hey, hey! The police are here.
Please watch out.
Let go of him.
Leave.
Get lost.
You started the fight.
And you're sitting here peacefully.
If you’re afraid,
why pick a fight?
If I beat them,
my punches will kill them.
Beat what?
Hey! Shut up.
You guys use fights just to pass time.
One day when your heads get cracked,
you'll understand.
They are rowdies.
Why do you bother them?
You should enjoy your college days
and set your life.
Idiots.
Always getting into petty trouble.
Oh no!
Go away.
He is leaving.
Fine, let him go.
Munna...
Aunty must have messaged him.
This is the story.
Cigarettes, alcohol and fights.
I thought this is all my life will be.
Then one day arrived and turned
my life upside down.
“Hail, Hail Ganapati
Ganapati Bappa Morya!”
“Hail Ganapati
My heart knew there was no one more beautiful
than her in the world.
Day and night,
I was lost in her thoughts.
"Something is beginning...
my body no longer feels at ease"
"Shall I see you fully, at least once?"
"My lips won’t open properly,
like a trembling sigh"
"A flash of lightning has struck my heart"
"Is this love? Is this love?"
"Is this what stirs such turmoil in my heart?"
"An unseen battle rages within,
while rain pours inside my chest"
"There it is,
my heart said and rushed forward"
"Innocently, it collided, burned
in a whirlwind of confusion"
"I stumbled, searched,
and wandered longing to see you"
"A melody, overwhelming and swift...
A tenderness I had never known before"
"A waterfall of floods of light
A playful dance for eyes that had never met"
"The rising beauty reveals its own story
The very first springtime of love"
"Perhaps she is here somewhere…
Somewhere here... "
"Perhaps she cannot be seen...
O heart… my heart…"
"In this hidden game, in the play of my heart…"
"Your image, your thoughts,
return again and again"
"A moment that joins like
a spark feels like a blessing"
"The weight of joyful dreams eventually tires,
scatters, and dissolves into restless chaos"
"Once found, may we never part
with our lives tied together"
"Let us stay united forever and
turn these timeless moments into our past"
"Let our hearts find rhythm and union
Let the coming ages belong to us"
"Something is beginning..."
"My body no longer feels at ease"
"Shall I see you fully, at least once?"
"My lips won’t open properly,
like a trembling sigh"
"A flash of lightning has struck my heart"
"Is this love? Is this love?"
"Is this what stirs such turmoil in my heart?"
"An unseen battle rages within,
while rain pours inside my chest"
“Is this love, is this love
the feeling that stirs a storm within my heart?”
“Is this love, is this love…”
"An unseen battle rages within,
while rain pours inside my chest"
Go to MeeSeva centre and pay the current bill.
What's wrong with you, Dad?
Is MeeSeva open on Sunday?
I don't even know what it is.
How can you be like this?
You can't even do basic errands.
How will you survive when I'm dead?
It is scary to think.
You are the only child.
So what if I am the only child?
If there were ten of us,
we’d all be playing cricket on the ground.
All age groups.
What are you requesting him for?
Sit down.
I will show you how to send him.
Give.
What is your problem?
What cricket team are you talking about?
I'll slap you.
Why does he keep saying
I’m an only child?
Spoiling my relaxed Sunday.
Oh!
You are so sweet.
Relaxing on a Sunday...
Don't you feel ashamed?
Shouldn't he stay home even on Sundays?
Do we have nothing to do
but stare at you?
You're on the streets everyday, anyway.
Would it hurt to pay the bill just once?
Mom, give it to me.
I am a slave in this house.
No worker relaxes at home like royalty.
When do you let me relax?
You turn off the fan everytime I sleep.
From the moment I wake up,
I carry water, pay bills,
and do all the household chores...
Bloody hell!
That's why you have me.
A worker would've cost you.
You see how he is talking.
Hey, hey...
Wait a minute.
Get me a packet of curd too.
-I need it.
-I won't get it.
Take from the neighbour.
Fine, don't get it.
Why should I take from them?
Oh gosh!
Why is everyone here?
Hey dear...
What is this?
Token.
Go and sit there.
Go to the counter when it's your turn.
Your bald head…(muttering)
This is pure torture.
Hey, mom.
What happened?
What's with these annoying people?
That's not your house.
Sorry.
For everything to be handed to you.
I can't do this, Mom.
You know how bad it is here?
Why are there so many people?
Obviously.
Someone here handed me a token...
Take it & stay in line.
Mom, I am very hungry.
I am coming home.
You hang up.
Next token number.
Give me the token.
Hey...
That day...
Is it really you?
Yes, it's me.
Do you work here?
No.
The chair was empty so I came and sat down.
-Oh!
-Get it?
How funny!
I was wondering what this angel was doing
among these aunties.
No mind.
Angel?
-You know I have seen you before.
-Is it?
You've no idea
how I searched for you.
I was also waiting for you
to come to me.
Why didn't you tell me before?
I would have come flying.
Flying?
Too much.
Token number 143
I was dreaming?
Not here?
Where did you go?
Give me the token.
Give me the bill.
Amount to be paid 622.
You should’ve carried change with you.
How can I provide change
if everyone brings 500?
Tell me.
Next token number.
Do you not even
look at the customer?
What is it, Sir?
Do you have another bill?
Sir?
Do you have more bills?
You remember me from that day
on Ganesh mela...
Next token number!
Please move.
Madam...
Can't you wait?
What are you looking at?
What was he saying?
He wants me to look at him and settle his bill.
Is this a marriage proposal,
to look at faces?
Yeah right.
Sunday 9 to 1.
We are one.
Monday to Saturday 9 to 6.
We are fixed.
Uncle...
From today, this is my office
as much as yours.
Yeah.
You are my salary.
Bye.
Is he mad?
Oh!
Lord Vishnu is chilling.
Okay.
-Mommy... Just a second.
-What's it?
Here is the curd you asked for.
Keep it there.
Move.
Okay.
Relax.
You have to tell me, Daddy.
If there is any work,
you have to tell me.
Didn't I pay just now?
I can do it again.
It's no big task.
Huh!
Come here.
What is it, Mom?
What's this?
What are you doing?
She is checking
if you were boozing
while paying the bill.
What do you mean?
You think I drink?
You sound out of character.
Did you step on something?
Or are you possessed?
You always say I do nothing.
When I do,
you two fool around with me.
You people think I am joke,
living in this house.
These are just errands.
Find some real work.
How long will you relax for?
Why do you always circle back
to me getting work?
And what work do you mean?
So petty.
At least call it a job.
Uneducated.
Tell her, Daddy.
I will find something.
Didn't you just call me possessed?
It's going to take time.
With my bamboo
I can beat any ghost out of you.
Is it a CC copy?
Is everything okay, Amulya?
-Hey, get up.
-Move.
-Get up.
-Move it I say.
I am asking you to get up.
What's this?
I came to check how long
the queue was.
Sure, I can tell what line
you're trying to get cleared.
Get out from here.
Only come with bills. Or else don't come.
Leave now.
Take your hands off me.
I'm going.
The groom has gotten his blessings.
Don't know.
Why should I care?
-He was staring at you...
-Date of birth?
Me?
No, I meant, me.
He was looking at me.
As a guard,
why aren't you standing at the door?
You can't come here casually.
You should come only with bills.
Move.
I will still come.
You will return with bills.
You think I'm a nobody, right?
I am backed by big people.
Okay, let us see.
Aunty, your power bill,
current bill, electricity bill...
-All three are the same.
-Right.
Water bill, tap bill, land bill...
Whatever it is, we will pay.
This is a social experiment.
It is social service.
It's social service. Right.
Bro...
We'll come later.
-Why?
-Let's go.
-Social service?
-Yes.
Or is it for a girl?
Let's go, Vikram.
He is one police dog.
Greetings, Aunty Sana.
You got any bills?
Who's bill? For what?
Get going.
She has given you good.
Move it.
What's this?
Go home and study.
-Bill? I don't have any...
-Uncle...
Bloody hell!
Damn!
Why is your street like this?
There is no respect here.
Let us go to my area.
They are respectful over there.
Is it?
Come on then.
-Do they have power here?
-Hi aunty...
Aunty...
Just one minute.
Aunty!
Who is that wild bear?
Shit
Respect...
Aunty...
Do you have unpaid electricity bills?
I have but I am not free.
Oh!
I'm here to help, Aunty.
Aunty...
How long more?
I'm looking for it.
Aunty...
Aunty, did you find it?
Still searching.
He cleaned up well.
I'm here to help, Aunty.
God bless you!
Check the money.
What is it?
I'm here to help, Aunty.
Aunty...
Do you have electricity bill due?
We will pay.
I am not free to give.
But he is here to help, Aunty.
Hey...
Don't you want the bill?
-Wash me properly.
-Yes, I am pouring.
All this for a girl.
Come, have a taste.
Here.
I will take care of these bills
and win over the girl.
Damn it!
What an embarassing lot you are!
Here is the baldy.
Take this bill.
You said you'll return with a lot of bills.
Give me the token.
One bill is what you got.
I will bring only one per day.
Is there a problem?
Give me.
I don't have a problem.
Make sure you don't cause one.
Token No.14
He is not here.
Add 10 to that and it'll be 24.
Can't you add?
Token No.14
Hello.
My number.
Sir, token.
So tiny!
Why are you at this counter?
Hey...
Watch your mouth.
-Sir, your bill?
-Hey, you.
Give me your bill.
She won't budge.
-Are you sure?
-Sit.
Come.
Okay.
You got to wait for you turn.
Hello...
You can't do as you please.
Do you understand?
Anyway...
Aren't you looking enough at her from there?
Up close...
Do you want to zoom and see her?
You can see temple from a distance...
But you can't see
the Goddess from a distance.
How would you like to pay your respects?
To the Goddess...
-I'll bow down.
-Oh!
Are you trying to be shy?
My name is not Babu.
Then what?
Baby?
Munna.
Then?
So what?
What is this baby's name?
She is not a baby.
Ammu.
Amulya.
-Amulya...
-Why are you hitting me?
It's too perfect.
Amulya means precious, right?
Swapna means 'like a dream'.
-Dream girl.
-Oh okay.
This is enough for today.
See you later, Dream girl.
Go and celebrate now
-O' Munna...
-Yes?
Your receipt.
Thank you, Dream girl.
Go on.
Why did you give him my name?
Sreenanna, I want gold facial.
It'll cost 500.
I will pay you from my dowry.
Who gives dowry in love marriage?
Oh my goodness!
What a thing to say!
Let's see if your tongue will manifest it.
Oh damn!
Go slow.
Don't finish him off.
That's his face.
I know her name now.
Who will stop me now?
I sent her a direct attack.
Token No.28
What is it?
The number is correct.
-Didn't you bring the money?
-Yes, I got it.
Sir...
Hey!
-Can you come?
-Ammu...
Why call, Sir?
Sorry. Madam...
Sorry, I will not repeat it again.
Hello, excuse me...
Hello, please...
What happened?
Sir...
Server seems to be down, Sir.
There shouldn't be any issue with server.
Check now.
Sorry.
Next token no.
Token?
Sit
Come.
Sit down.
Uncle...
I will come again tomorrow
with one more bill.
Cutie.
Eat on time.
Ammu, I love you.
He drew a heart too.
Didn't I tell you earlier that
he was coming for your service
and not our service.
Hey...
Why did you thrash it?
That is your very first love proposal.
Take it and get it framed.
Have you seen
a cheaper proposal than this?
We are poles apart.
Directly saying, 'Ammu I love you'.
That too on scribbling paper.
Look at the handwriting.
It is so bad.
What about the handwriting?
Were you going to give
extra marks for handwriting?
Dude, what a shocker…
She filed a complaint, but the moment he showed up,
she was like, ‘Sir, the server seems to be down.’
She really loves me, man.
"Such a wonderful feeling...
Such an amazing feeling"
"My fair-skinned girl, my beautiful girl...
She's fairer than a lizard"
"Soft, fluffy cheeks and adorable little lips
She's cuter than the cutest little child"
"While I'm brushing or flushing
Her face keeps revolving in my mind"
"The sticker on my bike carries her name
Even my password is her birthday"
"Such an amazing feeling..."
"If you want to experience a feeling like this,
you've got to fall in love"
"I love my milky-skinned girl...
Like a child going crazy for the first time"
How did I get so lucky that she's mine?"
"I love my milky-skinned girl...
Like a child going crazy for the first time"
How did I get so lucky that she's mine?"
"Even when she's skinny, she's beautiful
How adorable she'd be if she was chubby!"
"If she looks lovely in a churidar...
Then I'd die if I saw her in a saree"
"If she became daughter-in-law,
my parents would feel as if an angel entered the house"
"If she became my friends' sister-in-law...
They'd go crazy praising her"
"She's wonderful from every angle,
Once she's in my life, everything feels perfect"
"Such an amazing feeling..."
"If you want to experience a feeling like this,
you've got to fall in love"
"I love my milky-skinned girl...
Like a child going crazy for the first time"
How did I get so lucky that she's mine?"
"I love my milky-skinned girl...
Like a child going crazy for the first time"
How did I get so lucky that she's mine?"
What happening, Ammu?
Take your hand off me, sir.
Bloody idiot!
I should have slapped him.
For the love I had on her...
I would have killed him
if my friends didn't stop me.
But she still doesn't understand
my feelings.
That's why I chose to declare
my love for her
inscribed on my heart
rather than on a paper.
It's too simple, bro.
Couldn't you make it more stylish?
This is his handwriting.
And it's just as he wanted.
You wait, man.
Tell me...
You got the tattoo now,
but how do you remove it?
I don't think he will need that.
Come on, bro.
Poor chap.
Oh!
Being so extra.
Clearly he rushed through it,
now how will his wife react
when she sees this?
How will she feel
about another girl's name on her man?
Shut up!
You are such a negative guy.
Why will there be another girl in my life?
You don't stop.
I asked you to be quiet.
Bloody idiot!
Have you gone mad?
How can you beat up your friend for a girl?
To hell with you!
How is he wrong?
Don't you know
that she doesn't even care about you?
Forget all this, bro.
Apologize to him first.
Apologize now.
Let's go from here.
He has lost it.
He is on leave for a month.
I don't know
why someone hit him so bad.
Yeah, I know.
Poor him!
He is such a nice guy.
Ammu!
I have a feeling
that it's your guy who hit him.
Who is my guy?
Who else? It's the groom.
How many more days
will you call him my groom?
I feel so annoyed.
Oh, is it?
Did you catch feelings already?
Hey!
You have feelings
just looking at him?
Sure, that's how it is.
How about you?
Oh!
Being possessive?
I am not interested in your guy.
You keep him to yourself.
Possessive?
Who is he to me?
He means nothing to me.
I get irritated even to look at him.
How can you call me possessive?
O' God!
I pray he doesn't come here
for a few days atleast.
Not just for few days.
I wish he never comes back.
He looks at me
with his wild face, all day.
It makes me so uncomfortable.
Annoying.
Very irritating.
Useless fellow.
Bloody loser!
Idiots like him are a burden to Earth.
His parents are responsible for him.
How is it acceptable for such people
to be out in public?
Bloody rogues!
Bloody idiots!
To heck with his love!
Nonsense!
Ammu...
-Ammu...
-What?
Look there.
Munna!
Why did you talk like that?
He is hurt now.
What should I do then?
I hope he is so hurt,
he doesn't return.
Didn't you see him come?
I saw.
You come and do your work now.
I think you are stupid.
Useless fellow!
Bloody loser!
Idiots like him are a burden to Earth.
Don't you know
That she doesn't even look at you?
To heck with his love.
Nonsense!
How can you hit your friend for some girl?
She must see it.
-Hey!
-Yeah.
What happened there?
Few rascals showed up
And said mean things to the poor girl.
I kicked them out.
I informed the police too.
Can you call our number?
What happened, madam?
Or will you give your number?
Ask if she can handle two at once.
And also,
ask how many she can handle.
Token.
-I meant the token.
-Oh! -Token!
I don't wish for him to be there,
even when I die.
And I wouldn't care even if he were dead.
After a couple drinks,
they will unite,
and say,
'to hell with you' to us.
My brother didn't raise his hand on me till now.
But today, he did, and that too
for some random girl.
It's ok.
Forget it.
Oh God!
She is quite a beauty. Amazing!
He seems to really like her.
I too feel the same.
Something is wrong.
Hey!
Can't you see?
What's up?
Can't you see, Munna?
I can.
That's why I hit.
Why?
Are you overstimulated?
What rubbish were you talking there?
Where?
Oh, is that your girl?
Great catch, dude!
Let us get a share of her too.
Screw up, bastard!
Hey!
Stop.
Wait.
-I want to finish him off, by myself.
-Go for it.
He struck him.
Finish me off by yourself?
Jackass!
I'll smash each one of you today.
Get lost.
You moron!
You scoundrel!
Go on, try it—I dare you!
You won't be spared.
Come here.
Smash each one of us?
Smash each one...?
Hit me now.
Give him good.
Come and quickly hold him.
Get him up.
This douchebag!
-Hit him.
-Hit him hard. Go!
-What is it? Are you tired?
-Hit him hard.
Hit him good.
Beat this bugger down!
Brother...
Munna is getting beat up on the road.
Let's go.
Hey!
Why are you telling him?
They are not together.
They are in different directions now.
What say, Vikky?
Am I not right?
What do you think you are saying?
I will wreck every single one who touched him.
-Who the hell is it?
-Tony's boys.
Those jerks!
"We will die together"
"We will stand together"
"We belong to one another"
"I stand by my friend,
I stand by my friend"
"Watch out, we're coming"
"Run and hide behind your mother now"
"Wherever you may be,
Even if your father stands with you..."
"If you mess with my friend,
We'll make sure it's the end of you"
"I stand by my friend
I stand by my friend"
"Be careful, you'll be torn to pieces
You'll be gathering the pieces yourself"
"Even if your brother threatens us
Even if your mother pleads with us"
"We'll crack your ribs
We'll settle the score at your grave"
"We may argue and fight among ourselves
But our stories are ours to tell"
"We face our own fate ourselves"
God damn it!
Finish him off!
Get up.
I will break you to pieces.
Up!
Get up, I say.
To heck with you!
Wait, I'm coming.
Stop.
Stop. It's hurting.
Are you going to die for her?
See how he is thrashed.
You'd be killed if we didn't come.
He is one useless fellow.
Did you go and hide
when your friend is getting assaulted?
That kid is better than you.
Hey Chunky,
go get some tea.
What kind of a guy are you?
Is there no one more beautiful
than her in this world?
-Chasing this damn girl
for no good. -Hey!
Stop talking like that about her.
I will.
I'll definitely talk.
-If I didn't show up, you would be beaten
like a dog on the streets. -Hey!
Who asked you to come?
I'd be killed. My foot!
You ask if she's the only one?
Yes, she's the only one.
She is the most beautiful to me.
-I want this damn girl.
-Damn girl?
Didn't you ask me not to say that?
I can say that.
She's my girl.
But you cannot.
I will go any distance for Ammu.
Ammu, Ammu...
Just sit and chant her name!
That's how it is,
when you are in love.
O' Scientist, I beg of you.
Please don't intervine.
He wants to school me.
-Listen to me.
-Aye!
You can go above and beyond for
who appreciate you,
but she doesn't even notice you,
why would you fight for her?
Beautiful girls are more difficult to handle.
They have plenty of choice.
Trust me.
This damn girl will make your life hell.
Sorry.
Your girl.
First time,
I saw tears in her eyes.
I couldn't tolerate that.
I went to take down those guys.
He didnt understand
a thing I said, you see.
Please listen to him.
They are going to prey on you now.
You will be gone if they spot you.
Stop fooling us and going there.
If you go there without telling us...
Don't go there.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay to what?
-I won't go to her without telling you.
-Promise me.
-Promise me you won't go.
-No.
You want a promise?
What's wrong with him?
Fine.
I must seem crazy
for expressing my love
to you in writing, right?
Your supervisor harasses you everyday.
He is bed ridden for two full months.
I'm the one to beat him.
Tony's guys passed lewd comments at you.
I only beat them too.
And got beaten too.
Why is that?
I will do anything for you.
I am not useless.
I am a man.
And I'll take care of you.
And I love you.
And I want answer.
I thought you don't have feelings for me.
But after knowing so much
you still don't react.
Because you are heartless to feel anything.
You are ruthless and insensitive!
What grade are you in?
10 or 12?
I'm older than you.
What did you study?
Degree.
What was your score?
What is this?
Is there no place in your heart
unless my score is 99%?
Starting interviewing me.
Do you know my salary?
Government job.
It's a contract.
But I'll be permanent
from this year.
In the evening,
at home, I teach music.
That earns me 5000.
So in total,
I make Rs.20,000.
You?
Don't even make Rs.20
I can tell.
Go.
Earn 20k first.
Then come to profess your love to me.
I don't say I will accept you then.
You said you were a man, right?
Come back to tell me.
Otherwise the jokers from yesterday
or my supervisor,
are no different from you.
You trouble me everyday too.
Except you don't pass bad comments.
What do you mean?
If I earn Rs.20000,
will you be mine?
I knew it.
This is how you'd understand it.
Leave.
Find a job.
I will get one in no time.
Any call centre would pay me more
than you for my English.
Hello boss...
Yes...
I've a government job.
You find a government job too.
Go.
Why this condition?
It's so hard to crack
a governement job now.
Isn't it, Swapna?
It's true.
That's really hard.
Give me another option.
Exactly.
You can't do it.
Go.
Is there no other consideration?
-Next.
-Ok ok ok, done done.
Government job?
Done.
Deal.
Don't see me till then.
Not even with your bills.
I am serious.
Be careful.
Ahh...
Fine.
I will be in touch till then,
can give me your number?
Hey!
-Thank you, Swapna.
-What are you doing?
It's alright.
Poor guy!
He says he'll find a job for your sake.
Don't you think he needs motivation?
Hey, Munna...
Don't call or message her
because you've her number now.
Be happy looking at her picture.
-Don't come again.
-I will not come.
I will come only after I get a job.
You would wait for me, right?
You won't tell.
But your eyes do.
Government job...
It's confirmed.
You dialled 100.
What happened here?
Yes sir, some goons came by
yesterday and created a scene.
Even that boy over there comes here everyday
-Only to trouble her.
-Catch him.
Where are you guys?
Ammu gave me her number.
Why are you troubling that girl everyday?
-What's wrong with you?
-Hey...
What did you say?
Shut up and move it you idiot.
-What is this?
-Bloody fool!
Why are you hitting me?
-How dare you?
-Who do you think you are?
Bloody idiot!
So what if you're police?
So what?
Catch him.
Leave me.
Let go of me.
Why are you beating me?
Isn't she pretty?
Pass the phone quick.
Give it back to me or
I will lose my job.
Give it back.
That's enough.
Thank you, Sir.
Should I not see?
Sorry sir.
Oh! She is gorgeous.
You will make a great couple.
You see that?
Even Swami sir likes us.
You didn't like though.
Did we say that?
You don't have to.
I could tell from your faces.
I want to say
you are most lovely couple in the world.
Enough?
It is not so clear on the phone.
You should see her in person.
Then you will know.
That there is no one prettier
than her in this world.
She is beautiful beyond words.
She is such a catch.
She looks out of this world.
Here is tea.
Daddy, thank you.
Uncle, did you add ginger?
I did, madam.
Good boy.
I made tea as a kind gesture.
Now you have new demands. Look at her!
Ammu...
Stop that song for a minute.
-What?
-Munna...
Hit someone for calling you a female.
Just for calling you a female.
That too a police officer.
How much love does he have for you?
What?
You can go on about him
for another 100 years,
but I still don't want him.
You are right.
We reject those who care for us.
It's easier to find some moron to marry.
That's it, right?
Right.
What I did...
Hey, listen to me...
Hey, shut up.
Looking good.
Is he your son?
Yes sir.
It's difficult.
Sir, please don't say that.
He is a good man.
We know you can surely help him out.
Please sir.
How can I help?
Doesn't he know?
How to behave with a police officer?
He is a kid, sir.
He didn't mean to.
Have mercy on him.
That's tough.
Don't do that.
Don't offer him now.
Please accept this, Sir.
And let him go.
Bribing a police officer?
-No sir.
-Stand up.
Stand up!
Get out.
You stand up.
You trying to bribe a police?
Do you know what he did?
Please sir.
-He shouldn not have...
-What did I tell you? Get out.
Brother...
Do you know what your son did?
He is harassing girls on the road.
And you're trying to bribe.
He is beating up the police.
Is this how you raised him?
Munna...
Come out.
CA sir is calling you.
What for, sir?
Are you taking him for another dose?
Oh wow!
Only known each other for one day.
But you are friends already.
-Is that how tight you are now?
-Sir...
Let it be for one hour or one day,
our friends are for life.
Munna...
I'll be there for you.
Chintanna!
Remember that.
Move it.
Keep walking.
Why is you here, Daddy?
Why are you sitting here?
Get up.
Sir...
Why did you bring my dad?
Why is my dad here?
Get up, first.
Get up.
Stand up.
Shirt...
Where is his shirt?
-Give me my dad's shirt.
-Be quiet.
Why is my dad shirtless?
Why is my dad here for my mistakes?
What did you say?
For your mistakes?
-Where is he?
-Find out what happened.
Please come fast, sir.
File the FIR now.
We'll see who comes to rescue.
Munna...
Why are you sitting down?
Brother Shekhar, get up.
Stand up.
Sit there.
You sit down first.
Don't get tensed.
I am here now.
It's okay.
Just five minutes.
Sit here and watch.
What's up, sir?
Madhusudhan Reddy Sir.
Who are you?
You will know.
You will know
all about me in two minutes.
Can I see the FIR please?
You are a lawyer, is it?
Did you issue the CRPC notice?
No, I didn't.
I don't intend to either.
What are you going to do?
What can I do?
You striped him shirtless.
Now I will strip you.
Strip me?
Who do you think you are?
Huh?
Who allowed you to enter?
Hey!
Who brought him here?
Ramesh!
Out.
Take him out now.
So?
...
Really?
Yes, Meghana.
If I don't get my call
in the next three minutes, file the case.
Yes.
CRPC 57
And 331.
Meghana...
One second.
Do one thing.
Remove them.
We will go for 97.
Yes.
CRPC 1973
What case is that, sir?
Hebeus corpus.
Hey, release them.
Ramarao, Give his shirt back.
Sir.
Please leave, sir.
Shekhar bro...
This is very common.
Kids will be kids
I tell you.
Please relax.
Brother, why are you doing this?
Bro...
Thanks, bro.
Hey, hero.
Bro...
No, bro.
Don't call me hero again.
You are my hero.
You gave such a tough time to that CI.
It happens.
-I'll beat up that Madhusudhan Reddy one day.
-Sure.
You must beat him.
Beat him with education.
Beat him with success.
Education is everything for us middle class.
Notice how scared he was
when the two sections were mentioned.
This is education.
Go on.
Daddy is leaving.
Go.
Thanks, bro.
Dude, your daddy is leaving shirtless.
I offered to drop him but he refused.
Daddy...
Why are you walking like that?
Stop.
I asked you to stop.
Daddy.
Fine, go.
Bloody hell!
Do whatever!
Aunty, look there.
Uncle is coming.
What happened to him?
Why is he shirtless?
What happened?
Why are you coming like this?
What's wrong?
Tell me.
What happened to Munna?
Why don't you stop?
Tell me what happened.
Why don't you say anything?
Tell me.
What happened at the police station?
Why did you come back like this?
Where is Munna?
Daddy.
-Are you mad?
-Munna.
-What happened?
-What's wrong with you?
Daddy.
-He is not allowed in this house anymore.
-Munna...
Ask him to go away.
-He better leave from here.
I don't want to see him.
Tell me what happened.
You should tell me...
If you let him in,
he will kill myself.
Why is nobody telling me what happened?
What did he do wrong?
Why don't you tell me?
Is that how you kick him out?
If I leave now, I'm never returning.
You think I will come back?
Pushing me out of the house...
What's wrong?
-What happened?
-Why are you shouting?
He held me by my neck and pushed me out.
Don't shout.
Everyone is looking.
You keep quiet.
Shut up.
They let me go as it wasn't my mistake.
But he doesn't trust his own son.
What kind of a father are you?
I will never come back here again.
Munna...
I don't want to see your face,
I'm telling you.
I will go down a truck.
Bugger off!
What's this?
Have you lost it?
Don't come in between.
-Listen to me.
-Move.
Looks like he might harm himself.
Then let him!
Did you know your son has been harassing girls
out in the open?
And he admitted that he made a mistake.
Is he wrong or not?
How did he turn out like this?
I don't believe it.
-Hold him tight.
-Leave me.
-Stop, dude.
-Let go off me.
Just wait.
-Stop right there.
-Leave me.
You are going to die?
Are we not there for you?
Let's go home.
There is no need for that.
-Listen.
-Munna...
Go to his house.
Stay in his room.
You want to go under a truck for this?
Look at yoruself.
Did you eat or not?
-Come with me and eat.
-Take him.
I am famished.
I ate when I went to Ammu.
I was so hungry
and he kicked me out.
Forget it.
It's quite common.
What father is he?
You would know
if your father did the same.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Sai...
Bring Biryani.
Go with him.
Bring me chicken.
I don't want or need anything else.
Go.
Remember that guy
who said he can offer a conductor job
if we pay 50,000.
That Siddipet guy?
Are you in contact with him?
Why?
Do you want a job?
Uncle will be very happy to know this about you.
That's true.
If I get a government job,
Ammu says she will accept me.
Are you dumb?
How can you chase Ammu, after all this?
Look at him.
Fine.
So what if it is for her.
Atleast you will get settled.
That's good.
Pick up now.
Eat.
I won't be a conductor.
But I'll find something good.
Okay.
Let's find you a Collector job.
What is my darling doing?
Type it.
Is my angel sleeping?
Don't break the flow.
Ammu, did you eat yet?
Love.
You dumbo!
Hi Ammu.
This is Munna.
Good night.
Sweet dreams.
Love you.
This is how sweet it should be.
It's my first message.
Use a heart.
Come on.
Send a heart.
My heart is with her anyway.
He doesn't know all this.
My poetry is better.
Ammu...
Where are the rubber bands?
Just check near the mirror.
How long will your upma take?
Making upma and taking forever...
This is from Munna.
Didn't she throw it away?
What happened?
Upma is ready.
Shall we eat?
We will eat upma later.
Come here.
What is it?
What?
Come.
Sit here.
What's it?
What is this?
Where did you find this?
Huh?
Where?
Where did you find it?
Just wait.
I will pick it up.
So, that is how much you like him.
I knew it.
What's problem with telling me?
Did you tell yourself
how much you like him?
What do I do, Swapna?
Munna doesn't know my reality.
He is only attracted to my face.
If he sees me like this,
he will get shocked and run away.
Then I will have to kill myself.
I can't take it.
That's why,
I asked him
never to see me again.
And I won't see him either.
This is only for a few days.
I will forget him soon.
You can't do it.
Yes, I can.
I know this.
You'll love him more but not less.
Think about it once.
Maybe he will accept you
if who you are.
Even if he accepts,
won't his life get spoiled?
How will he spend all this life with me?
He deserves
a good girl.
That's it.
For the first time in my life,
I questioned why I wasn't normal
like the rest of the girl and cried, you know?
For the first time.
I feared he would see my clutches,
and hid them under the table.
When he was present,
worried he might see me,
I wouldn't leave from my place,
and ate lunch at the table.
I wore lipstick for him as well.
I lost my mind.
I don't understand why.
Why not?
That's love.
That's how it works.
There is no rule that you can't be in love.
Yes, there is.
"To your eyes, I may seem like moonlight"
"But inside I am an unseen flame"
"If I become the cause of your pain,
I cannot bear it"
"Like an eye without eyelids"
"Like a little child without a mother..."
"If I become a burden to you,
I cannot go on living"
"How long can I hide my feelings for you?"
"How long can I suppress this storm within me?"
"I can't do it anymore...
Don't chase me"
"I can't endure it anymore..."
"Please don't come after me"
"Even if there were something greater
than the sky itself..."
"Unable to tell you that you are my world,
I die a little every day"
"In my world soaked with bitter memories..."
"If your companionship is not there,
I am no longer myself"
"This wandering heart would simply stop beating"
"My love, smile just once"
"Believe me, I would give you my life"
"I can't do it anymore..."
"Don't chase me..."
"I can't endure it anymore..."
"Please don't come after me..."
Vacancy at the Panchayat!
Not happening.
Hindi teacher wanted in school.
We can't work at schools and shelters.
What is this?
This is not possible.
This is a bank post.
You need to be good at math.
You are not!
He won't do this.
He cannot work here.
He won't be able to do this.
If I can't do this, how can he?
He is just a kid.
Exercise?
-He never exercised in his life,
how can he now? -Hey...
That's called excise.
It handles alcohol taxation.
Is it?
You seem to know everything.
Why don't you search?
Idiot.
Hey!
What?
Is there nothing for me?
Looks difficult.
What a challenge she posed for you.
Not this way.
Now what?
Does she only want a government job?
You will make more money
selling snacks.
That's true.
With his qualifications,
he can’t even sell tea on a train.
Don't blow on me.
Why?
Is it going to kill you?
Don't be dramatic!
How long do you need?
Dude!
He missed the most important one.
-What did I miss?
-Look here.
Hey!
This is too difficult.
But it can be great for you.
It's a good one.
Think about it, Munna.
You must salute every SI and CI.
You will do their household chores.
Sooner or later, wash their toilets too.
Right, Sai?
When a new constable joins,
surely there’s ragging in the department.
He can wash toilets for his love.
Won't you wash?
There...
Next to it.
Before constable ad.
There is an SI, isn't it?
Don't you see that?
Are you blind?
-Oh! Please wait.
-You fools...
SI?
What do you think you are?
A lion?
Tell me the full form of SI.
Isn't it 'Singam Inspector'?
What rubbish!
'Circle'.
Circle Inspector.
That's CI.
Oh!
'Circle' Inspector.
He is right.
Hey!
Whatever the Inspector is.
This is what I want.
It's the best for me.
That's it.
Sure.
Let's go.
Done.
What say?
Hey!
First,
-I must tell Ammu.
-Hey!
Stop there.
Wait, dude.
Your head is always filled with Ammu.
Stupid.
If this fails,
you'll lose all respect.
Wants to inform Ammu already...
He is always ready for it.
Come.
Why do you always talk negatively?
-You and your silly face.
-Tut!
-Walk, idiot!
-Why are you hitting?
A constable’s life is like a dog’s.
Brother, I don't want to be a constable.
Then?
He wants to be SI.
You want to be SI?
Yes.
Straight up SI?
Not possible.
Have you ever chased anything in life?
Except for girls?
Do you even have a life?
Apart from smoking and drinking?
Competition will be less.
Try for Constable job.
Do you hear me?
A servant's son is a servant.
Not a master.
Whenever you saw me,
though no one cared,
you would always ask
when I would change to be better.
Now, I want to improve.
So, I come to you for help.
But you looked down upon me.
Makes me sad, Uncle.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Hey, Munna.
Come here.
What is it ?
If you make it as an SI,
I’ll be the first to salute you.
Do you understand?
Go and meet Coach Ranjith
in C ground.
He will train you well.
You can surely be SI.
I can't do this anymore.
-Hey, what happened?
-What wrong? -I can't do this.
-How many do you smoke in a day?
-Sir...
You can barely run.
Panting like an old man.
Get going.
Sir.
No sir.
I will work hard.
It's not meant for you.
Don't waste time.
-Leave.
-Sir.
Please don't, Sir.
-I can do it, sir.
-Go.
Come, let's leave.
-Just go.
-Why are you pleading him?
-Who are you guys?
-Bloody heck!
Keep walking.
-No chance you'll be an SI!
-You begging him? -Buzz off!
Why are you blaming him?
Then?
What should we do?
Mad fellow.
He is too extra.
My girl was right.
That I can't do it.
She asked me to get a government job
just to avoid me.
Hey, don't overthink it.
Take it easy.
Look here.
This is my message from that day.
There is still no reply.
What do I think?
She will surely reply.
I'll share you my poetry.
She has to reply.
Please smile now.
Why are they everywhere we go?
Hey, dude...
Yes, bro.
What are these girls doing here?
Munna wants to be an SI.
He is dancing while running.
Is it?
So?
You want to be an SI?
He's going to be an SI.
You can be his driver.
And drive him around.
Go to his house every morning
and polish his boots.
Polish, polish.
Polish his boots.
-Let's finish them.
-Hey, relax.
Munna, back off please.
Running, jumping...
is not meant for you.
Go home and sleep.
Hey, leave me.
Bloody coward!
-You are so dead.
-I will kill you.
Hold him.
Listen to me.
Please don't fight.
Hey, get up.
Get up.
Hey..
-Catch him tight.
-Want to hit me?
Come hit me now.
Hey, that looks like Muuna, isn't it?
Hey, move away.
Beat him now...
What are you looking at?
I will beat you up to pulp
if I see you in this ground again..
Hi, Chintanna.
What are you doing here?
I came to beat up some coach.
-That is who you beat up just now.
-Really?
Good.
My work is done.
-He told him he’s not fit even to be a home guard,
let alone an SI. -Ooh!
And he is requesting that guy.
Is he the only one to train you?
Aren't we here?
Yeah right.
Brother.
This is not drinking competition.
-Is it?
-It is SI training.
Hey...
Do you want to see how goons like us
will train you to become an SI?
Huh?
Hey, Munna...
You will be a police officer.
You will marry your girl.
And we will come to bless you.
That is for sure to happen.
Trust me.
Yayy!
"Start our guy’s training!"
"This is where it begins, son!
Run bro… "
"Come on, run bro!"
"From today, running must become your heartbeat"
"Your legs must race like your heartbeats"
"The fat beneath your skin must fly away"
"Become smooth and fit like a boiled egg"
"Run, boy!
Come on, run!"
"Run bro… Come on, run bro!
Run bro… Hey, run bro!"
"Who was that guy who commented you?"
"I'll tear his shorts and teach a lesson!"
"Show him the fire and make him regret it"
"Show your commitment to those who commented on you"
"Feeling hungry, brother? I’ll bring you a protein shake"
"If you even say biryani, I’ll punish you hard"
"With Don Chintu's coaching,
I'll make you win medals"
"I’ll build your thighs
strong like Usain Bolt"
"Brother, such wise words from you
gave me goosebumps I say"
"All the narrow streets with potholes
must become your training ground"
"Your hard work must turn
the whole path green with success"
"When you remove your socks,
even your ankles should bleed"
"A movie should be made
saying 'Run Munna Run'!'”
"Run bro… Come on, run bro!"
"Run bro… Hey, run bro!!"
"Run, boy!
That's it, run!"
Okay!
That's greats news.
Finally, he has started looking for a job.
Is uncle still angry now?
Speak softly. He's right here.
He didn't misbehave with anyone.
He really likes that girl, Aunty.
Have some tea.
She's the one
who told him to find a job.
"Come on, come on boys,
be on the mission"
"It’s warm-up time,
take your position"
"Stretch, stretch, stretch...
Stretch like a crane"
"Hop, hop, hop...
Hop like a squirrel"
"Jump, jump, jump...
Jump like a frog"
"Run, run, run...
Run like a cheetah"
"Pick up the stick…
throw it into the air"
"Spin the ball…
reach your goal"
"You must strike back, Munna!!"
"The ones who doubted you
The ones who abandoned you"
"The backstabbers
The ones who wished for your downfall"
"Tomorrow all their mouths must be shut"
"They must burn seeing Munna’s victory"
"Run bro… Come on, run bro!"
"Run bro… Hey, run bro!"
"Wake up!
Lace up!"
"No rest, go get it"
"Fall down, rise up
One dream, work hard"
"Train hard, stay strong
Unlock beast mode"
"Train hard, stay strong,
unlock beast mode"
"Don’t quit, drop sweat
Face the race, love the pain"
"Love the pain… love the pain…"
“Don’t accept tiredness until victory arrives
Run like a cheetah until the very end”
“Shake off your failures, don’t carry sadness
Show your courage, write your story into history”
“Don’t stop moving, leave your sleep behind
Half-hearted efforts, are never enough”
“Fall again and again, but keep taking steps forward
The final turn, is where victory waits”
“Say goodbye, to your daydreams
The path of blood and sweat, is the warrior’s chant”
“Half is pride, half is attitude
Mix them together, and run… run!”
Oh wow!
Those goons have trained you well.
You'll soon be SI.
And very soon, I will marry Ammu.
We shall have a daughter.
She'll look just like Ammu.
Like a doll.
-Let's take a selfie.
-Sure.
Here is our Sunday special.
Hmm... Mutton.
That's all?
Won't you eat?
I will eat later.
My stomach is upset.
Why is that?
This mutton looks smacking.
What wrong?
My sister-in-law cooked.
How's it?
I didn't ask.
Bloody scoundrel!
Munna, wait.
-Just wait.
-Let me go.
-All drama.
-Please stop.
Munna, wait.
Please listen.
Munna!
Hey...
Why would you throw away food?
Just shut up now.
Bloody hell!
Kicked me out of the house and sent me
mutton to eat?
Are you mad to shout like this?
-Keep quiet.
-You think I've nothing to eat?
Whatever it is!
How could you throw away food?
You think I am a begger?
I don't need your help.
Understand?
Now that I gave it back
ask him to relish it properly.
Don't say such things.
I don't want their fake love.
Leave me alone.
Didn't I say no?
He made me cook for him and send.
Did you see
how he flung it?
Im not a good guy, Ammu.
I hurt my mom alot today.
Why i want to share everything with you, Ammu?
You didn't care anything!
Once, please give a reply, Ammu.
Hey...
-What is it?
-Come here.
My brother is there.
Hand this to him as rent.
Return his own money to him?
It's okay, just do it.
I'll also come.
Ramanna...
What's up?
-Here.
-What's that?
It's...
Rent for staying in your house.
Take it.
What is he to me?
He's your brother.
What about you?
If he's my brother, what are you to me?
Aren't you my brother?
You think you are so grown up to pay me rent?
Keep it inside.
I'm sorry, brother.
I heard
you've passed the written exam.
-True.
-Eat well. Train well.
You're must become an SI
not Constable.
Not an SI that accepts bribes.
I'll come to your police station to wack you.
-Fine.
-It's okay. He can take bribes.
Shut up.
You think everyone is cunning like you?
You will have problems.
You should overcome them.
That's where respect is.
Learn from your father.
Do you realise how respected
Mr. Shekar is in our area?
He is very well-respected.
Munna...
I know your father from before you were born.
Sure.
I should learn from him.
To kick his own son out of the house.
So?
So what now?
Brother...
You can talk about anything but that man.
That man?
That's your father you are taking about.
What do you know about him?
Training for two days got you in bed.
He works for ten hours straight everyday.
Have you ever seen what he does?
He is up on his feet from morning to night.
Bloody hell!
His boss doesn't even provide a chair to sit.
Every day, your mother massages his legs.
Did you ever ask?
Why his legs hurt so much?
Or did you massage his legs ever?
A father’s legs endure the most strain.
God doesn't live in temple, churche or mosque.
Your mom and dad are the real Gods.
Why does he work so hard?
Isn't it for you?
You think you grew up by yourself?
And you have the audacity to call him 'man'?
Do you know you use half his salary
just for your pointless whims?
No matter how much you cry
when they are gone, they won't return.
You should take good care of them
while you can.
Our parents are the happiest
when we succeed in life.
We must win only for them.
What is he doing there during exams?
I am coming.
Ok.
Hey, what is this?
Why are you coming?
I am Ammu's friend.
Can you come with me please?
What happend?
Is it Polio?
Actually
She is without both legs.
Your friend doesn't know.
He always looked only above the table.
He didn't notice this.
Oh God! Poor guy.
How can this happen to him?
Gosh!
How do we tell him now?
He thinks he has the most beautiful girlfriend
and a perfect love story.
His love fell apart, just like mine.
I don't know how to tell him this.
God damnit!
-Why don't you say anything?
-Hey, stop it.
What is your problem?
Stop rattling about it.
We are not telling him now.
We will see when he lands the job.
All the best for tomorrow, Munna.
Sit properly.
Hey, Vikram...
Munna...?
Vikram?
Vikram...
Get up.
-Who the hell are you?
-Vikram...
-Hey, move it.
-Hey!
What's up, fatso?
You are always the first to run.
Why are you still here today?
Take him and escape.
What about you, hero?
You want to be an SI?
How can you run
when I break your legs?
Like this?
I will smash your face first.
You scoundrel!
You move aside.
-I will kill you all.
-Leave from here.
-Go away.
Don't get involved. -You?
They will finish you off.
Move it.
I will die.
It's okay.
You leave.
Will you go or not?
Go, I say.
Hey Munna,
just leave.
Why will I go?
Are you mad?
You must leave.
Go on.
Listen to me.
If you don't go now,
you won't get a job tomorrow.
There will be no Ammu in your life.
Please leave.
Go!
Munna, run.
Damn it.
Leave him.
Hold him tight.
Hold him.
Bloody fatso!
VIKRAM!
Make him stand... Make him stand...
Make him stand...
Hold him... Hold him...
Munna, why did you come back?
I don't care about the job or the girl.
-Let it be.
-Will you go or not?
His head is broken.
Take him to the hospital, you fool.
-Munna...
-Get up.
His head is broken.
-Vikram...
-His head craked. Moves.
-We must leave now.
-He is dying.
Get up.
Please start.
Let's go.
Aunty, Munna is beat up.
Hey Anusha...
Come.
-Munna?
-They'll make a scene now.
Munna...
What happened to him?
Nothing.
Leave it, Mummy.
-We got into a fight.
-What do you mean?
What kind of fight?
Come home.
I don't want to come.
-Hey... I'll slap you.
-That's not my house.
Don't do this.
Come inside.
Your mom is calling you in.
Go now.
-Come inside.
-Nothing happened. Relax.
Sit.
What's this?
How did you get hurt?
Who's that?
Who hit him?
Tony's gang attacked us.
Gosh!
You got hurt badly.
-Let's go to the hospital.
-We're coming from the hospital.
They said not to worry,
it's a minor injury.
What happened?
Someone hit him.
Let's go to the police station and file a complaint.
How can we be quiet about it?
Look how badly they hit him.
Nasty fellows!
I am fine, mummy.
How can you say nothing happened?
You got hurt badly.
How are you fine?
Don't you have final exam tomorrow?
You don't have to attend that.
Uncle...
He worked very hard for it.
It's a minor injury.
He'll go tomorrow.
How can he go?
No need to go.
No need, Munna.
Don't go.
Who is he?
He is our friend, aunty.
Namaste!
Who is it?
Is it Tony's gang?
Yes.
It's them.
Come Vikram.
We'll drag them out and beat them to dust.
-Okay, let's do this.
-Stop Vikram.
Chintanna...
Forget about hitting them back.
-What are you saying?
-I'll run, tomorrow.
And land that job.
I don't want anything else in this life.
Please bro.
I already hurt my parents a lot.
That's it.
We must stop this.
Okay... Your wish.
Munna...
Hey!
Are you sure?
Can you run today?
Mummy...
Munna...
Are you ready?
Have some sweetened curd.
Good boy.
Why don't you take dad's blessings too?
He didn't go the shop
worried about you.
Hey...
Atleast inform him.
Good.
He left on time.
Come.
I'll make tea for you.
What happened?
Why did you come back?
"Have tears gathered in your eyes?"
"As I gently lift
your face from your cheeks..."
"Hidden somewhere deep within you..."
"A battle has taught you what strength truly is"
"How can the one who merely watches know..."
"...the pain borne by the shoulders that carry the burden?"
"A treasure beyond any price, my dear..."
"It was hardship itself that raised and shaped you"
"Wounds are the provisions for
the journey to your destination..."
"The supplies for the road ahead"
"It's training...
it's preparation..."
"Even the fiercest storms are training"
"It's training...
it's preparation..."
"Even obstacles are training"
Hello, boss!
I have a government job.
You also crack a government job.
Go!
Ammu, you would wait for me, right?
"Again and again,
your image appears before me"
"Day and night,
I only think of you"
"Revealing yourself to me
with every opening layer"
"Appearing even with every batting eye"
"It's her, everywhere..."
AMMUU...
Hello.
I'm Munna's friend.
What is it?
He got the job.
He is coming to meet her.
Is it?
We didn't tell him.
-We won't either.
-Okay. Fine.
He'll be stunned
when he finds out.
Where are you now?
We are in the backstreet.
She better not come from tomorrow.
Ask her to get transfered.
Okay, I'll do something.
Looks like it's going to rain.
Shall we wait for some time?
Shall we wait till it starts raining?
Let's go now.
Actually... a friend is coming.
We can meet her and go.
Surya, place them there.
Who is this friend
I don't know about?
Is Munna coming?
Tell me the truth, Swapna.
How would I know if he's coming?
Tell me the truth.
Tell me.
He is coming.
Why don't you meet him?
He cracked a Government job.
He won't leave
even if he sees you like this.
You know it, right?
That I don't have
the courage to meet him.
If you are really my friend...
I am telling you seriously.
I will kill myself I tell you.
-Send him off. Make him leave.
-Ammu...
Send him away.
Make sure he doesn't come here.
Tell him something and send him away.
Please.
-Ask him to go.
-Not now.
We should stay here.
He might be around.
He will see you for sure.
I will send him away.
You wait inside.
Wait inside.
Surya, lock the door.
Munna will come now.
Don't let him know anything about Munna.
Okay?
Didn’t I say
we should’ve come earlier?
Swapna, stop.
-Hi!
-Munna...
Didn't see you in a long time.
Did you forget?
Your friend asked me to meet
only after I get a job.
She is not here.
I think she moved to Delhi or Mumbai.
Delhi? Or Mumbai?
I don't know, Munna.
Her entire family has moved.
Really?
Please, Swapna.
She doesn't even reply to me.
Where do I look for her now?
Tell me if you know, Swapna.
Please.
Forget it.
She is not meant for you.
What's wrong with you?
Have you gone mad?
Are even friends?
Don't you understand?
-She's saying...
-Ammu is gone.
We don't know
where she went.
Why are you talking like this?
Swapna, tell me.
Where did she go?
I don't know, Munna.
Really.
Uncle...
Munna...
Surya...
Tell me, Surya.
Do you know, Surya?
Do you know
where Ammu has gone?
I don't know.
She hasn't been coming to office.
Fine, don't tell me!
-I'll find her. -She's not here.
Why don't you understand?
-Munna...
-Move. -Listen to me.
First hear me out.
Hey...
Please don't cry.
What is this?
Don't cry like a fool.
She is not here.
What can you do?
Where will you go?
Move aside.
Munna...
Please don't cry.
What is this?
Munna.
Let's go home.
You start that bike.
Munna!
Swapna...
You are hiding something, right?
Tell me, Swapna.
Please, Swapna.
Tell me where Ammu is.
You really loved her, didn’t you?
-So?
-What's all this?
She loves you even more.
Ammu also loves me.
I knew it.
But...
But she won't meet you.
She's not interested.
If she doesn't want to meet, let's go.
-We should go now.
-What's wrong with her? Is she mad?
She says she will quit her job
if you see her.
She says she will die.
Munna...
Not fair.
-She says she will kill herself.
-She will die.
Please leave, Munna.
She is disabled in her legs.
Is that her problem?
Did you know that?
-Do I know?
-How did you know?
What do you mean if I know, Swapna?
Doesn't she know that I know?
Didn't you know this?
That's not at all a problem for me, Swapna.
It means nothing to me.
I didn't tell them about it
as they wouldn't understand her.
How can I not know, Swapna?
After the first time I saw her
I came again the next morning.
I saw her on the scooty then.
My heart sunk, Swapna.
I cried the whole day.
I cried a lot.
But what can I do?
I can't stop loving her.
I keeps growing every day.
Do you love her out of sympathy?
What about sympathy?
I am mad about her.
She makes me feel love, lust, anger, everything.
I have all kinds of emotions for her.
For a minute...
My heart skipped a beat for a moment.
Let's go.
Take me to her.
Tell her that Munna has got the job.
Let's go, Swapna.
Let's go to her.
Tell me.
You tell her.
She is right here.
Tell her.
Inside?
Go, tell her.
Ammu...
Ammu.
Surya, open the door.
Ammu...
Ammu.
Open the door.
Why did you close the door?
I love you, Ammu.
I hate you.
Go away.
Leave
Look at my face and say
that you hate me.
Then I will never show my face again.
What?
I got the job.
Government job.
So?
You said you'll accept me if I get a job.
I got now
I said that
to make you go away.
Don't say that, Ammu.
I love you, Ammu.
I don't love you.
Leave.
Okay.
I will go away.
But I don't want to live.
Oh God!
I don't want to live a life without you.
Come here.
Come.
Stand here.
What are you doing?
Just watch me.
Look at me now and say.
Do you still love me?
And cannot live without me?
Leave it.
Why are you covering again?
I can't live without you, Ammu.
Please.
Please, go away.
Okay.
You also come with me.
Oh God!
Please, Munna.
Please.
I can't do this.
If you ever regret
or get frustrated after marrying me...
I can't bear it, Munna.
I will be.
I will be frustrated.
You'll also get frustrated.
I will annoy you a lot.
We must have all emotions
that a husband and wife have.
We should laugh, cry, beat, scold, kiss, love and live together.
I can't let you spoil your life.
I can't do that.
I don't see life without you, Ammu.
I will kill myself.
I will also kill myself.
No, Munna.
No.
Again...
You will get angry tomorrow.
If you get irritated,
you will hit me.
Then, you also hit me.
Hit me now.
Come on, beat me.
Hit me.
I Love you
I Love you, Munna